Guide to the Elizabeth Bishop Papers, circa 1880-2023 (bulk 1929-1979)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES I. CORRESPONDENCE
  - Letters to Elizabeth Bishop
    - Methfessel, Alice, [approximately 1971 Sep 25]; (1 letter) (Folder 116.23)
    - Methfessel, Alice, 1971 Dec 26; (1 letter) (Folder 116.24)
    - Methfessel, Alice, 7-[24] 1972; (6 letters, 1 greeting card) (Folder 116.25)
    - Methfessel, Alice, 1972 Jun 25-29; (5 letters, 1 news clipping) (Folder 116.26)
    - Methfessel, Alice, [1972] Jul 1-11; (6 letters) (Folder 116.27)
    - Methfessel, Alice, 1972 Jul 12-18; (7 letters) (Folder 116.28)
    - Methfessel, Alice, 1973 Mar; (4 letters) (Folder 116.29)
    - Methfessel, Alice, 1973 Dec; (1 letter, 1 greeting card) (Folder 116.30)
    - Methfessel, Alice, 1973 Dec 29; (1 postcard) (Folder 121.11)
    - Methfessel, Alice, [approximately 1973]; (1 greeting card) (Folder 116.31)
    - Methfessel, Alice, 1976 May-Jun; (5 letters, 4 news clippings) (Folder 116.32)
    - Methfessel, Alice — Birthday cards, undated; (7 greeting cards) (Folder 117.1)
    - Methfessel, Alice — Get-well cards, undated; (3 greeting cards) (Folder 117.2)
    - Methfessel, Alice — Valentine's Day cards, undated; (3 greeting cards) (Folder 117.3)
    - Methfessel, Alice — Miscellaneous cards, undated; (7 greeting cards) (Folder 117.4)
    - Methfessel, Alice — Newspaper clippings, 1978, undated; (2 clippings) (Folder 117.5)
    - Meyers, John Bernard, 1977; (1 letter) (Folder 22.20)
    - Mickley, Loretta, 1979; (2 letters) (Folder 11.3)
    - Miles, Josephine, 1964-1965; (2 letters) (Folder 11.4)
    - Miles, Josephine, 1968 Oct; (1 postcard) (Folder 124.13)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1935 Aug-Sep; (6 letters) (Folder 11.5)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1935 Oct-Dec; (4 letters) (Folder 11.6)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1936 Jan-Feb; (5 letters) (Folder 11.7)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1936-1937; (4 letters) (Folder 11.8)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1942-1943; (10 letters) (Folder 12.1)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1945-1946; (11 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 12.2)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1947-1949; (9 letters, 5 postcards) (Folder 12.3)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1950-1954; (15 letters) (Folder 12.4)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1956-1959; (11 letters, 1 fragment) (Folder 12.5)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1960-1973, undated; (14 letters, 6 postcards, fragments) (Folder 12.6)
    - Miller, Margaret, 1974 Jan 11; (1 postcard) (Folder 117.6)
    - Mizener, Arthur, 1946 Dec 31; (1 letter) (Folder 22.21)
    - Mongan, Agnes, 1959-1960; (2 letters) (Folder 12.7)
    - Moore, Henry, 1957 Jan 23; (1 letter) (Folder 22.22)
    - Moore, Janet, 1958 Feb 12; (1 letter) (Folder 22.23)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1935; (5 letters, 1 letter to M. Moore from Harper Brothers) (Folder 13.1)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1936 Mar-Jun; (5 letters) (Folder 13.2)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1936 Jul-Dec; (11 letters, 2 pp. TS) (Folder 13.3)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1937 Jan-Feb; (4 letters) (Folder 13.4)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1937 Mar-Dec; (7 letters) (Folder 13.5)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1940; (2 letters) (Folder 13.6)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1942 Jan-May; (5 letters) (Folder 13.7)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1942 Jun-Nov; (5 letters) (Folder 13.8)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1943 Jul-Sep; (5 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 13.9)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1943 Oct-Dec; (9 letters, 1 cc to M. Moore from U.S. Navy) (Folder 13.10)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1944 Jan-Aug; (6 letters) (Folder 14.1)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1944 Sep-Dec; (10 letters) (Folder 14.2)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1945; (9 letters) (Folder 14.3)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1946; (5 letters) (Folder 14.4)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1947; (5 letters) (Folder 14.5)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1948; (9 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 14.6)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1949; (6 letters) (Folder 14.7)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1950; (8 letters, 1 fragment) (Folder 14.8)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1951; (12 letters, 1 letter to M. Moore from Donnelly Fellowship) (Folder 15.1)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1952; (7 letters) (Folder 15.2)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1953; (3 letters) (Folder 15.3)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1954; (5 letters) (Folder 15.4)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1955; (4 letters) (Folder 15.5)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1956; (6 letters) (Folder 15.6)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1957; (2 letters, l postcard) (Folder 15.7)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1958; (3 letters) (Folder 15.8)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1959; (5 letters) (Folder 15.9)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1960; (3 letters) (Folder 15.10)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1961; (5 letters) (Folder 15.11)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1962; (4 letters) (Folder 15.12)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1963; (4 letters) (Folder 15.13)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1964; (3 letters) (Folder 15.14)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1965-1966; (5 letters) (Folder 15.15)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1967-1968; (13 letters, 1 letter to Roxanne Cumming from M. Moore) (Folder 15.16)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1969 undated; (2 letters, 1 fragment) (Folder 15.17)
    - Moraes, Vinicius de, 1968-1971; (2 letters) (Folder 16.1)
    - Morgan, Frederick, 1978; (1 letter) (Folder 16.2)
    - [Morse], Mary [Stearns], [1964] Jun 8; (1 letter - originally enclosed with 15 June [1964] letter from Lota de Macedo Soares to Elizabeth Bishop) (Folder 114.16)
    - Moss, Howard, 1954-1979; (8 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 16.3)
    - Muchnic, Helen, 1978-19; (3 letters) (Folder 16.4)
    - Mullen, Richard, 1978; (2 letters) (Folder 16.5)
    - Muser, Curt, 1978; (2 letters) (Folder 16.6)
    - Muser, Frani, 1935-1947; (5 letters) (Folder 16.7)
    - Muser, Frani, 1956-1962; (5 letters) (Folder 16.8)
    - Muser, Frani, 1964-1969; (6 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 16.9)
    - Muser, Frani, 1970-1976; (9 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 16.10)
    - Muser, Frani, 1978-1979, undated; (6 letters, 2 postcards, 2 greeting cards) (Folder 16.11)
    - Muser, Frani, [no year] Oct 4, 10; (1 postcard) (Folder 121.11)
    - Nemer, José Alberto, 1973; (1 letter) (Folder 16.12)
    - Nemer, José Alberto, 1974; (3 letters) (Folder 117.7)
    - Nemer, Linda, 1973-1974; (7 letters) (Folder 117.8)
    - Nemer, Linda, 1979; (1 letter) (Folder 16.13)
    - Neruda, Pablo, 1942, 1968, undated; (2 letters - one on a menu; 2 postcards - one sent to Marjorie Stevens) (Folder 16.14)
    - [Neruda?], Pablo, Lilli [Correia de Araújo] and Vinicius de Moraes, 1968 Sep 13; (3 notes on one postcard packet) (Folder 121.15)
    - Nims, John F., 1979; (2 letters, 1 cc from E. Bishop) (Folder 16.15)
    - Norris, Leslie, 1974 Apr 21; (1 letter) (Folder 22.24)
    - O'Connor, Flannery, 1958-1963; (7 letters) (Folder 17.1)
    - O'Donnell, Mark, 1968; (1 letter) (Folder 17.2)
    - Oliveros, Alejandro, 1978; (1 letter) (Folder 17.3)
    - Osser, Maya, 1968-1977; (3 letters) (Folder 17.4)
    - [Page?], Chester, 1972, 1977; (1 letter, 1 Christmas Card) (Folder 22.25)
    - Paz, Octavio, 1969-1979; (7 letters, 7 postcards) (Folder 17.5)
    - Peech, John, 1971-1977, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 17.6)
    - Pereira, Stella, 1968; (1 letter) (Folder 114.17)
    - Pereira, Stella, 1969; (1 letter) (Folder 17.7)
    - Petere, José Herrera, 1943-1944; (7 letters) (Folder 17.8)
    - Pettit, Millicent [Sabine Farm owner], [1978?] Sep; (2 letters) (Folder 22.26)
    - Pfeifer, Pauline, 1949; (13 letters) (Folder 17.9)
    - Pfeifer, Pauline, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 113.17)
    - Pfeiffer, Virginia, 1946-1949; (8 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 17.10)
    - Pfeiffer, Virginia, 1950-1964, undated; (13 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 17.11)
    - Pierson, [Miss?], 1975 Mar 28; (1 letter - photocopy) (Folder 22.27)
    - Pinsky, Robert, 1979; (1 letter) (Folder 17.12)
    - De Planck, [ ? ], 1974 May 11; (1 letter) (Folder 22.28)
    - Pollitt, Katha, 1978; (4 letters, 1 cc from E. Bishop) (Folder 17.13)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne, 1959-1973; (1 letter, 1 postcard) (Folder 17.14)
    - Portinari, Candido, 1958; (1 letter) (Folder 22.29)
    - Prentiss, M.E., 1948; (1 letter) (Folder 17.15)
    - Purdy, James, 1956; (1 letter) (Folder 17.16)
    - Raffaelli, Sylvia [wife of Mercelo], 1965 Mar 12; (1 letter) (Folder 22.30)
    - Rahv, Philip, 1956; (2 letters) (Folder 17.17)
    - Ramos, Donald, 1974; (3 letters) (Folder 117.9)
    - Rodman, Selden, 1975 Dec 15; (1 letter) (Folder 22.31)
    - Rorem, Ned, 1953, undated; (1 letter, 1 postcard) (Folder 17.18)
    - Rosen, Norma, 1973-1974; (2 letters) (Folder 17.19)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1979; (1 letter) (Folder 17.20)
    - Russell, Charlotte "Sha" and Red, 1973 Dec 4; (1 postcard) (Folder 121.11)
    - Sargent, Kay Orr, 1977 Dec; (1Christmas card) (Folder 22.32)
    - Schmidt, Michael, 1971-1972; (2 letters, 1 cc from E. Bishop) (Folder 18.1)
    - Schwartz, Lloyd, 1978; (1 letter) (Folder 18.2)
    - Serge, Victor, 1943; (1 letter) (Folder 18.3)
    - Sexton, Anne, 1963-1973; (4 letters) (Folder 18.4)
    - Shapiro, Amran, 1978 Feb 12; (1 letter, 1 poem) (Folder 117.10)
    - Shapiro, David, 1973 Oct 3; (1 letter) (Folder 22.33)
    - Shapiro, Meyer, 1959-1979; (3 letters and Elizabeth Bishop's lecture notes) (Folder 18.5)
    - Shaw, Robert, 1977; (1 letter) (Folder 18.6)
    - Sheehan, Rhoda (VC 1934), 1971 Feb 27; (1 letter) (Folder 22.34)
    - Sheehan, Rhoda (VC 1934), 1971, 1976, 1978; (2 letters, 2 postcards, 1 enclosure) (Folder 117.11)
    - Shore, Jane, 1978-1979; (2 letters) (Folder 18.7)
    - Slater, Candace, 1973 Oct 16; (1 postcard) (Folder 117.12)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1964] Jun 15; (1 letter - envelope also contained 8 June [1964] letter from Mary [Stearns Morse]) (Folder 114.18)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1964] Jun 17; (1 letter) (Folder 114.19)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1964 Jun 18; (1 letter, 2 fragments from 2nd page) (Folder 114.20)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1964 Jun 23; (1 letter) (Folder 114.21)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1964 Jun 26-29; (4 letters - in same envelope, 2 news clippings) (Folder 114.22)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1964] Jun 29; (1 letter) (Folder 114.23)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1964] Jul 4; (1 letter) (Folder 114.24)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1964 Jul 5; (1 letter) (Folder 114.25)
    - Miscellaneous clippings found with correspondence from Lota de Macedo Soares, 1964; (3 clippings found folded together) (Folder 114.26)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jun 6; (1 telegram) (Folder 118.1)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 4-6; (1 letter) (Folder 118.2)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 14; (1 letter) (Folder 118.3)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo - "About our wills,", 1967 Jul 14; (1 letter) (Folder 118.4)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 19; (1 letter) (Folder 118.5)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 19; (1 letter) (Folder 118.6)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 20; (1 letter) (Folder 118.7)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [approximately 1967 Jul 20-24]; (1 letter) (Folder 118.8)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1967 Jul 24?]; (1 letter) (Folder 118.9)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 27; (1 letter) (Folder 118.10)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 28; (1 letter) (Folder 118.11)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 28; (1 letter) (Folder 118.12)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Jul 28; (1 telegram) (Folder 118.13)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 2; (1 letter) (Folder 118.14)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1967 Aug 2]; (1 letter) (Folder 118.15)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 3; (1 letter) (Folder 118.16)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1967 Aug 7]; (1 letter) (Folder 118.17)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 8; (1 letter) (Folder 118.18)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 8; (1 letter) (Folder 118.19)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 12; (1 letter) (Folder 118.20)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 16; (1 letter) (Folder 118.21)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 17; (1 letter) (Folder 118.22)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1967 Aug 18]; (1 postcard) (Folder 118.23)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, [1967 Aug 19]; (1 letter) (Folder 118.24)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 25; (1 letter) (Folder 118.25)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Aug 28; (1 letter) (Folder 118.26)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 [Aug 30 or Sep 3]; (1 letter) (Folder 118.27)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Sep 7; (1 letter) (Folder 118.28)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, 1967 Sep 8, 16; (2 telegrams) (Folder 118.29)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo, undated; (1 postcard) (Folder 118.30)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo — fragments, [1967]; (4 fragments) (Folder 118.31)
    - Soares, Lota de Macedo — empty envelopes, 1967; (2 envelopes) (Folder 118.32)
    - Soares, Maria Elvira Macedo, 1967 Oct; (2 letters) (Folder 117.13)
    - Soares Regis, Flavio de Macedo, 1964-1970, undated; (10 letters, 1 postcard, 1 fragment) (Folder 10.1)
    - Soares Regis, Flavio de Macedo, 1968-1969; (8 letters, 1 enclosure) (Folder 114.27)
    - Solow, Robert M., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 22.35)
    - Souza, Decio Soares de, 1967 Oct 1; (1 letter) (Folder 117.14)
    - Spicer, Jim, 1972; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - Spiegelman, Willard, 1976-1978; (2 letters) (Folder 18.9)
    - [Staines?], David, 1974 Jul 7; (1 postcard) (Folder 121.11)
    - Staines, David, 1979; (1 letter) (Folder 18.10)
    - Stanford, Donald E., 1977 Dec; (1 Christmas card) (Folder 22.36)
    - Stapleton, Laurence, 1978-1979; (3 letters, 1 mailgram) (Folder 18.11)
    - Sternberg, Carolian and Hilgard, 1969-1976; (7 letters, 1 postcard from E. Bishop, draft translations of poems from Portuguese, curriculum vitae) (Folder 127.15)
    - Sternberg, Ricardo, 1978-1979; (3 letters, 1 cc from E. Bishop) (Folder 18.12)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1942 Oct 31-Nov 11; (6 letters) (Folder 18.13)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1942 Nov 14-20; (5 letters) (Folder 18.14)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1944 May 16-Aug 9; (8 letters) (Folder 19.1)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1944 Aug 11-30; (7 letters) (Folder 19.2)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1944 Sep; (9 letters) (Folder 19.3)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1944 Oct-Nov; (7 letters) (Folder 19.4)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1944 Dec; (6 letters) (Folder 19.5)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1945; (10 letters) (Folder 19.6)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1946 Jan-Feb; (8 letters) (Folder 20.1)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1946 Mar-Apr; (4 letters) (Folder 20.2)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1946 Jul-Sep; (6 letters) (Folder 20.3)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1948; (5 letters) (Folder 20.4)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1954-1955; (5 letters) (Folder 20.5)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1956-1957; (4 letters) (Folder 20.6)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, 1958-1959; (5 letters, 1 fragment, 1 letter from Sara Kent) (Folder 20.7)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, undated; (9 letters) (Folder 20.8)
    - Stevens, Marjorie, undated; (7 letters, 1 fragment) (Folder 20.9)
    - Stevenson, Anne, 1971-1980; (2 letters to E. Bishop, related correspondence) (Folder 21.1)
    - Strand, Mark, 1974-1979; (4 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 21.2)
    - Summers, U. T., 1968-1979; (5 letters) (Folder 21.3)
    - Sweeney, Jack, 1955-1958; (2 letters) (Folder 21.4)
    - Swenson, May, 1958-1960; (4 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 21.5)
    - Swenson, May, 1958-1979; (8 letters, 1 greeting card, 1 postcard) (Folder 21.6)
    - Swenson, May and R.R. "Zan" Knudson, 1970 Dec 24; (1 postcard) (Folder 121.11)
    - Tate, Allen, 1954; (2 letters) (Folder 21.7)
    - Taylor, Peter, 1974 Sep 7; (1 postcard) (Folder 121.11)
    - Taylor, Peter and Eleanor, 1972-1975; (2 letters) (Folder 21.8)
    - Temple, Ruth, 1978; (2 letters) (Folder 21.9)
    - Thacher, Barbara Auchincloss, 1971 Aug 31; (1 letter) (Folder 22.37)
    - Toklas, Alice B., 1959; (1 letter) (Folder 21.10)
    - Toklas, Alice B., 1968 Dec 16; (1 letter) (Folder 117.15)
    - Trainer, Mary, 1976 Feb 6, undated; (1 letter, 1 Christmas card) (Folder 22.38)
    - Travisano, Thomas, 1978-1979; (2 letters) (Folder 117.16)
    - Unterecker, Jack, 1977-1979; (5 letters, 1 postcard, 3 cc from E. Bishop) (Folder 21.11)
    - Untermeyer, Louis, 1948-1949; (2 letters) (Folder 21.12)
    - Updike, John, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 21.13)
    - Valdez, Faustina, 1944; (1 letter) (Folder 21.14)
    - Valentine, Jean, 1979; (1 letter) (Folder 21.15)
    - Van Doren, Mark, 1953; (1 letter) (Folder 21.16)
    - Van Spanckeren, Kathryn, [1977?] Dec; (1 Christmas card) (Folder 22.39)
    - Vendler, Helen, 1977-1979; (5 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 21.17)
    - Wakoski, Diane, 1975; (1 letter) (Folder 21.18)
    - Wallace, Emily, 1972 May 22; (1 letter, 1 photocopied bibliography) (Folder 117.17)
    - Walsh, Dorothy, 1978; (1 letter) (Folder 21.19)
    - Wanning, Tom, 1949, [approximately 1969 May], [approximately 1972]; (3 letters) (Folder 117.18)
    - Wanning, Tom, 1951-1970; (1 letter, 4 postcards) (Folder 21.20)
    - Ward, Aileen, 1973, 1978; (2 letters) (Folder 117.19)
    - Ward, Aileen — Correspondence re membership at the Cosmopolitan Club, 1978-1979 (Folder 117.20)
    - [Ward?], John - See Rukeyser letter of 3/20/79], 1978; (3 letters) (Folder 5.11)
    - Wehr, Wesley, 1979; (1 letter) (Folder 21.21)
    - Welty, Eudora, 1948; (1 letter) (Folder 21.22)
    - White, E. B., 1977; (1 letter) (Folder 21.23)
    - White, Katharine S., 1949-1976; (7 letters, 1 cc from E. Bishop, 1 fragment) (Folder 21.24)
    - Williams, Floss, 1958; (1 letter) (Folder 21.25)
    - Wilson, Edmund, 1945-1956; (3 letters, with 1 letter from Ferris Greenslet) (Folder 21.26)
    - Worth, Irene, 1966; (1 letter) (Folder 21.27)
    - [ ? ], Elizabeth [about the Diary of Helena Morely], 1955 Feb 28; (1 letter) (Folder 22.40)
    - [ ? ], Hilda, [1969] Mar 12; (1 letter) (Folder 114.28)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, A – Z, 1943-1978; (5 letters, 3 postcards, 2 telegrams, 2 greeting cards, 1 invitation, 1 receipt) (Folder 21.28)
    - Fan mail, 1934-1979; (16 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 22.1)
    - Christmas cards, A – Z, 1977; (19 cards, 1 letter, 1 photograph) (Folder 22.2)
    - Christmas cards, miscellaneous, 1977; (6 cards) (Folder 22.3)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence — Students (Folder 117.21)
    - Empty envelopes, (2) (Folder 124.12)
    - Unidentified [Adrienne? Marienne?, circa 1971; (1 postcard) (Folder 127.14)
      Removed from Bishop's copy of The Selected Poems of Howard Moss,
      Grille PS 3525.O8638 A17 1971
  - Letters from Elizabeth Bishop
    - To Andrade, Carlos Drummond de, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 38.8)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1964; (2 letters) (Folder 112.1)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1965 Feb-Jul; (14 letters) (Folder 112.2)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1965 Jul-Dec; (11 letters, 1 letter to Dr. Celso Motta re: Ouro Prêto) (Folder 112.3)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1966 Jan-Jun; (11 letters) (Folder 112.4)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1966 Sep-Nov; (8 letters, 1 telegram, 2 letters from Maria Carlota de Macedo Soares ("Lota") to Araújo) (Folder 112.5)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1967; (19 letters) (Folder 112.6)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1968; (10 letters) (Folder 112.7)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1969; (7 letters) (Folder 112.8)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1971; (1 letter) (Folder 112.9)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, 1972 ?; (1 letter) (Folder 112.10)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, undated; (8 notes and letters) (Folder 112.11)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, undated; (3 lists of things to be done) (Folder 112.12)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli, undated; (8 recipes) (Folder 112.13)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli - postcards [interfiled with chronological correspondence in use photocopies], 1966-1971, undated; (14 postcards) (Folder 112.14)
    - To Correia de Araújo, Lilli - postcards/photos (4 picturing Ouro Prêto, 1 snapshot of Elizabeth Bishop), undated; (3 postcards, 2 photos) (Folder 112.15)
    - To Arnold, Ned [David Shapiro's editor?], 1973 Oct 26; (1 letter) (Folder 38.9)
    - To Bartlett, Lynn C. [Secretary, Vassar College], 1968 Mar 12; (1 telegram) (Folder 38.10)
    - To Baumann, Anny, 1947-1949; (9 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 23.1)
    - To Baumann, Anny, 1950-1954; (19 letters, 3 postcards) (Folder 23.2)
    - To Baumann, Anny, 1955-1959; (26 letters) (Folder 23.3)
    - To Baumann, Anny, 1960-1964; (18 letters) (Folder 23.4)
    - To Baumann, Anny, 1965; (21 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 23.5)
    - To Baumann, Anny, 1966-1969; (32 letters, 3 postcards) (Folder 23.6)
    - To Baumann, Anny, 1970-1973; (13 letters, 4 postcards) (Folder 23.7)
    - To Baumann, Anny, 1974-1979; (14 letters, 6 postcards) (Folder 23.8)
    - To Baumann, Anny, undated; (8 postcards, 1 clipping) (Folder 23.9)
    - To Belitt, Ben, 1977-1978; (1 letter, 1 postcard, 1 thermofax reply from Belitt) (Folder 99.7)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1949; (1 letter) (Folder 24.1)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1952; (4 letters) (Folder 24.2)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1953; (l9 letters) (Folder 24.3)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1954; (11 letters, 3 postcards, 1 fragment) (Folder 24.4)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1955; (10 letters, 2 postcards) (Folder 24.5)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1956; (10 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 24.6)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1957; (6 letters) (Folder 24.7)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1958; (8 letters) (Folder 24.8)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1959; (12 letters) (Folder 24.9)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1960; (6 letters) (Folder 24.10)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1961; (10 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 24.11)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1962-1963; (2 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 24.12)
    - To Bell, Pearl K., 1968, undated; (5 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 24.13)
    - To Bishop, Aunt Florence [Jane], 1955; (14 letters) (Folder 98.1)
    - To Bishop, Aunt Florence [Jane], 1956; (13 letters) (Folder 98.2)
    - To Bishop, Aunt Florence [Jane], 1957; (15 letters, 5 postcards, 1 empty envelope) (Folder 98.3)
    - To Bishop, Aunt Florence [Jane], 1958; (12 letters) (Folder 98.4)
    - To Bishop, Aunt Florence [Jane], 1959; (16 letters, 6 postcards) (Folder 98.5)
    - To Bishop, Aunt Florence [Jane], 1960, 1966; (11 letters, 5 postcards, 1 empty envelope) (Folder 98.6)
    - To Bishop, Aunt Florence [Jane], undated; (2 letters, 3 fragments, 4 postcards, 1 empty envelope) (Folder 98.7)
    - To Blacmer, Donald L. M. (of M.I.T.), 1977 Jan 15; (1 carbon copy) (Folder 38.7)
    - To Booth, Philip, 1973, 1978-1979; (2 letters, 3 postcards) (Folder 25.1)
    - To Borden, Fanny, 1934 Jun 26; (1 letter) (Folder 38.11)
    - To Bottrall, Ronald, 1956 Jul 22; (1 letter with envelope) (Folder 114.8)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1950-1952; (2 postcards) (Folder 25.2)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1955; (2 letters) (Folder 25.3)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1956; (5 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 25.4)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1957; (3 letters) (Folder 25.5)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1958; (4 letters) (Folder 25.6)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1959; (6 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 25.7)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1960; (9 letters) (Folder 25.8)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1961; (7 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 25.9)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1962; (8 letters) (Folder 25.10)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1963; (9 letters) (Folder 25.11)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1964; (7 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 25.12)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1965; (10 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 25.13)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1966; (4 letters, 3 postcards) (Folder 25.14)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1967; (3 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 25.15)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1968; (11 letters) (Folder 25.16)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1969; (6 letters, 3 postcards) (Folder 25.17)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1970; (4 letters, 7 postcards) (Folder 25.18)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1971; (10 letters, 5 postcards) (Folder 25.19)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1972 Jan-Jun; (9 letters, 6 postcards) (Folder 26.1)
    - To [Bowers], Aunt Grace, 1972 Aug-Dec; (8 letters, 4 postcards) (Folder 26.2)